I'm Julie. [cheering] I'm the host of
the show. Thanks for watching. Welcome
to Hollywood. We're glad to have you
here.
[cheering]
Summer is almost on us. It's And I
[applause]
Things are feeling [cheering]
things are, dare I say, things are
feeling a little bit good lately, right?
And I know there's definitely an air of
jubilation in New York. Around 2 million
Knicks fans took to the streets today to
celebrate their first NBA title since
1973. All the players were on display.
There's Spike Lee. There's Ben Stiller.
All the big super fans were there.
Timothy Shalomé. He's going to need a
vacation. He's given a lot of energy to
this series. Tracy Morgan was there. Um
Martha Stewart showed up. Uh they had
the fans were jocking for
position, I guess. And
>> [cheering]
>> You get a spanking.
>> Oh man, I [cheering]
>> I got to tell you, I hope Martha Stewart
didn't see that. That's [laughter]
I feel like that's the image they should
print on all the New York license
plates, you know. And then uh they they
made their way to city hall where Mayor
Mom Donnie presented the players with
the key to the city, which is exciting.
There's Jaylen Brunson as opposed to
his, you remember his predecessor, New
York's former mayor a few years ago,
Eric Adams, presented the key to the
Diddy. And
oops,
obviously that key doesn't work on every
lock.
The owner of the Knicks, James Dolan,
yesterday said his team will accept an
invitation to visit the White House so
the players can officially hand their
trophy over to the president in person.
Is there any chance James Dolan asked
the team before he accepted that on
their behalf? He might be in for a
surprise if he didn't. What if they
don't want to go? Maybe Dolan figures he
could just put some random tall black
guys in Nick's jerseys and Trump won't
know the difference. Mr. President, this
is Carl Anthony Towns. But it's all very
exciting. The president will get to hold
a trophy that stands just the same way
he does.
Same color, too. [cheering]
All the celebrities
who weren't in New York for the parade
showed up in Chicago today for the grand
opening of the Obama Presidential
Center. Look at this lineup of
musicians.
Bruce Springsteen, [cheering]
Christina Aguilera, Common, Eddie Veter,
Jennifer Hudson, John Legend, Mark
Anthony, Marseilles Martin, The Root,
Stevie Wonder, Tames, Bono, and The
Edge. I guess they couldn't get vanilla
ice. What a bunch of losers.
All the living presidents were on hand.
Minus one, of course. Bill and Hillary
Clinton showed up. George and Laura Bush
were oop be careful there. President
Bush Joe Biden and Jill Biden were at
the event. Sasha and Malia were there to
support their mom and dad. [cheering]
And of course Barack and Michelle, which
[applause]
Donald Trump was not invited to the
ceremony, which is a shame because the
Obama Center has a library, a vegetable
garden, a gym. So many things Trump has
never seen.
Obama gave a speech. He did not mention
the orange one. And neither did
Michelle, though she did manage to land
a subtle little jab while listing her
husband's many accomplishments.
>> Ending a war, ordering the Bin Laden
raid, saving an auto industry, winning a
peace prize.
[cheering]
>> [cheering]
>> keeping us safe from Ebola,
regulating the banks.
>> She's explaining it to Bill. We just saw
the moment Hillary's edible kick in.
[laughter]
I miss seeing people who smile run the
country. Meanwhile, there's no smiling
in Trump land right now. Donald Trump is
having a really bad week after this
dummy of a deal he signed off on. Even
his own side is against him on this.
Trump should reneg. Iran deal faces
backlash from conservative allies. And
that's not from MSNBC. That's from the
liberal Democrats over at Fox News.
Trump got a copy of this memorandum of
understanding they came up with last
night during his dinner with French
President Emanuel Mcronone. You can see
here he is putting his little Don
Hancock on the retreaty of Versailles.
Unfortunately, that's the dessert menu
he signed. So, he got a macaroon to go.
And then he got a big round of applause
for I don't know what for accomplishing
nothing. Once again, the deal is Iran
gets billions of dollars and then we'll
talk about a deal. It's a deal to make a
deal. It's hosted by Howie Mandel. It's
going to be terrific. They still haven't
they still haven't even gotten into the
details of the nuclear stuff, which is
interesting because three months ago,
Trump wrote no deal with Iran except
unconditional surrender. Little did we
know he meant it was ours.
So, in the end, after all of this,
Trump's answer to the questions, who did
you go to war with and how did it end
will be the same answer. Iran.
I um [cheering]
thanks everybody. [applause]
>> Thank you, G. You're welcome.
>> I feel like you didn't get that at all,
did you?
>> No, [laughter]
>> I was not listening.
>> Thank you for the unconditional
[laughter] support.
Well, I hope you're paying attention
this summer because I I will be taking
the next two months off. This time
voluntarily. Um,
but we have assembled a potent group of
hosts to fill in for me, beginning with
Tiffany Hattish, Coleman Domingo, Ike
Baron Holtz, Anthony Anderson, Jelly
Roll, and as a special treat for our
commander-in-chief, I asked one of his
all-time favorites, Rosie O'Donnell, to
be here to keep the hooks coming. So,
[cheering and applause]
You're welcome. And all I ask in return,
Mr. President, is that you don't do
anything stupid while I'm gone. Okay.
We're three days now away from the first
official day of summer. And before that
happens, I want to take a minute just to
mention one of the unsung heroes of the
summer season. And that is this, the
humble pool noodle. Now, on the surface,
it's just a tube made out of the same
things Jared Kushner is made out of, air
and foam.
But it's so much more than just that.
You can sit on it. You could spoon with
it. You can do this with it. Make your
nephews laugh. The pool noodle was
invented in Canada, believe it or not,
where it is almost always too cold to
use one. Why they invented the pool
noodle, I don't know. But the real
mystery is how did this get in my house?
I have never purchased a pool noodle. I
don't know where they're even sold. I
don't know where you buy one. And yet, I
have at least half a dozen of these in
my backyard. No idea how I got them.
They just appeared one day like 67. It
was just all of a sudden there.
We don't know where they're coming from,
but what we do know is that you can
drink out of them. And since I'm headed
out on vacation, I [cheering] thought
why not
[applause]
a little [cheering]
Did you get it?
[cheering]
Okay.
[laughter]
You little sneak. Uh, by the way,
Father's Day is on Sunday. The first
Father's Day uh will here. That's for
you. was celebrated in 1910, though it
did not become an official holiday until
1972. And if you think about it, what
could represent dads more perfectly than
taking 62 years to finish a project,
right? I mean, so [laughter]
what the what was that? Was that a
horse?
>> I have a delivery for a Jimmy Kimmel.
>> Oh, hi. I'm Jimmy Kimmel. What's the
delivery?
A giant horse
for me
>> and a baby horse, too.
>> Well, I didn't order a horse. I didn't
order either of those.
>> I'll bring the little one in.
>> Oh, no. Don't bring the little one in.
[laughter] Do we don't need the Oh, you
want the little one out? I don't know.
Did you order a horse? I didn't order
anything. [cheering and applause]
>> No more pizza. Did you order that horse?
>> No,
>> I DIDN'T ORDER.
I don't [applause] There's tequila all
over the floor. I didn't order this
horse. I don't know what it's doing
here. We're doing the show right now.
>> I need you to sign for it.
>> I don't want to sign. I just don't want
it. I want to reject it. You can send it
back.
>> Here, I'll sign for you.
>> What are you going to do with it?
[laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I just
>> enjoy your horse.
>> Yeah. Thank you. I don't want the horse
in here. Can we get somebody to get the
horse out of here?
>> [music]
[cheering]
>> A yeah.
Oh wow. [cheering] I don't want the
horse in here. The horse is here and
there's no kickbacks, I did it. I
am here, BABY. [cheering]
>> Ladies and gentlemen, thank you.
I have traveled [applause] far and wide
through waves and war to save this
audience
from mediocrity.
[cheering]
What? What is this? This is trespassing.
This is another crime you've committed
here.
>> Your face is a crime.
>> How long have you been hiding in that
horse for this?
>> Did the Knicks win?
>> Yeah. You if you leave quickly, you can
go catch the end of the parade. Okay.
What are you doing in here?
>> What does it look like, dumbass? I'm I'm
on your show. I'm promoting a new movie.
It's coming out July 17th. [cheering]
[applause]
>> You know,
is it called We Bought a Horse?
>> No, it is called The Odyssey.
[cheering]
>> It's It's It's based on a book, so you
probably don't know about it. [laughter]
>> Oh my god. Did you ser Did you do this
movie specifically so you could sneak
into this room in a Trojan horse? That
is the saddest thing I've ever heard.
What a loser you are.
>> I I did this movie so I could say that
horse is a Trojan, which is something
your dad should have used on his
[cheering]
on his on his little wiener instead of
having you.
>> My father has a huge penis. I'll have
you. [laughter]
>> Your mom said mine's bigger.
And [cheering]
guess what? You know what? My ploy
worked because I made it on the show. I
did it and you couldn't stop me.
[cheering]
>> Yeah.
>> You're not on the show.
>> Oh, really? I'm not on the show. Okay.
What? Cuz it seems like I am. I
>> Hi, Jimmy's audience. Hi, everybody.
>> Oh, wait. The audience at home. Do you
still have an audience?
>> Yes, I still have an audience. Don't get
in. That's my camera.
>> There you go. There. Nope. Nope. Nope.
All right. See, hey, everybody at home,
you can wake up now because [laughter]
because the show is finally finally good
for like a minute. All right. You know,
[cheering] that's [applause]
>> You want a noodle, mother? Noodle.
>> I will I will noodle all day long.
>> Oh, you will, will you? Huh? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ah, come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. No.
NO. [screaming]
OW. What are you trying to do?
YOUR NOODLE IS SOFT. THAT'S NOT WHAT
YOUR NOT WHAT YOUR MOM SAID.
[cheering]
>> All right.
>> Are we done?
>> Yeah, I'M GOOD. [cheering] NO,
>> I'm sorry. Seriously, I just want to say
seriously, thanks for having me on your
show.
>> I didn't have you on the show.
>> You did? You had me on. Everybody,
please go see the Odyssey. We're going
to be right back with Larry David.
[cheering]
>> I say we'll be back with Larry David. We
will be right back with Larry David.
[cheering]